https://www.everettbank.com/privacy-policy

Notice
You are continuing to another website.
Everett Bank does not control the content of any external website and make no warranty, expressed or implied,
regarding the accuracy or content of any external website. In addition, we advise you to review their online
Privacy Policy.
Switch Kit
Download our Switch Kit to help guide you through switching your accounts to Everett Bank.
Download
Online Banking
Bank when and where you need to. Managing your finances is easier than ever before.
Register
Order Checks
Click the link below to re-order your personal checks online.
Switch Kit
Download our Switch Kit to help guide you through switching your accounts to Everett Bank.
Download
Order Checks
Click the link below to re-order your personal checks online.
Facts
WHAT DOES EVERETT CO-OPERATIVE BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies can choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit certain aspects of this sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depends on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number
Income
Account balances
Payment history
Transaction history
Credit history
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to help run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information, the reasons why we choose to share and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Everett Bank share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus.
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
No
We don't share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiences
No
We don't share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
No
We don't share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We don't share
Questions? Call 617-387-1110 or go to www.everettbank.com
How does Everett Bank protect your personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards along with secured files and buildings. We also maintain other physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.
How does Everett Bank collect your information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
Open an account
Apply for a loan
Give us your income information
Apply for financing
Provide account information
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
What can I limit from sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
Information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates from using your information to market to you
Sharing of information to nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
Definitions:
Affiliates:
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. Everett Bank has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates:
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. Everett Bank does not share with nonaffiliates for marketing purposes.
Joint Marketing:
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. Everett Co-operative Bank doesn't jointly market.
Other Important Information:
We will not share personal information from deposit or share relationships with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization
